COME ON
Come on!
owareru youni
Running like a fugitive,
isoi de iru
being chased by something.
kawai ta mune ga
Inside my heart is pounding,
kari tateru no sa
my throat dry like it's withering.
dare no tame de naku
For no single one,
dare no mono de naku
to none does belong,
ore tachi no ima ga
this time is ours, right now...
itami hodoki kokoro hodoki kage o hodoki
Unraveling the pain, unraveling our hearts, unraveling shadows.
iki o tsunete hashiri nukero yami o saite
Stifling our breath, reaching for beyond, tearing through the dark.
tatakau koto mo aishi au koto mo
In fighting and in love.
owari wa shinai
To the distant light above,
ON THE WAY
yes, we are on the way!
I WANNA ROCKS mune ni ROCKS
I wanna rock... Rockin' my heart...
Sasuke here at Point B!
Sakura here at Point C!
Naruto here. I'm at Point A!
You're slow, Naruto!
Okay, the seventh team...
Hm?!
The target has moved!
Follow it!
Alright! It's over there!
What's your distance
from the target?
Five meters!
I can go at anytime!
I'm ready, too!
Me, too...!
Okay...
Do it!
Uryaaah!
I got him!
Does he have the ribbon
on his right ear...?
Are you sure it's our target Tora?
It's the target, no mistake.
Alright, the mission to capture
lost pet "Tora" is complete!
Isn't there a mission
with a greater sense of urgency?!
Impor-
tant
Mission!
Heading to the
Land of the Waves!
Oh! My cute Tora-chan!
I was worried to death!
The Wife of the Land of
Fire's Feudal Lord
Madame Shijimi and Tora (the Cat)
Serves him right, that stupid cat!
No wonder he ran away...
...Now, then!
The next mission for
Kakashi's seventh team is...
An errand to the neighboring town...
to babysit the Chief Councilor's boy...
Helping with digging
for potatoes, eh...
No!
No! No, thank you!
As for me,
I want to do like
a more exciting mission!
Give us something else!
He's got a point...
Man... He's a pain!
I thought it was about time
for him to get fretful...
You fool!
You're still bottom rookie!
At the start,
everyone moves up
the ladder
by gaining experience
from simple missions!
B-But!
It's been nothing
but blah missions so far!
Knock it off!
Naruto!
It's necessary to explain to you
what a mission is...
Listen to me!
Requests pour into the village
every day.
They range from babysitting
to assassinations...
A wide spectrum of requests are
recorded on the request list...
They are separated into A, B, C,
and D ranks in order of difficulty.
In the village,
everyone below me
is divided up by ability in the order of
Jonin, Chunin, and Genin.
We at the highest level distribute
the requests as missions
to Ninja who have abilities
that suit said mission.
And, if the mission is successful,
the fee comes in from the client.
Nevertheless, you guys
have just become Genin...
Rank D is about
the best you can do...
Hm?!
Yesterday's lunch was pork-bone
broth noodles,
so today will be miso broth...
Listen!
I-I'm sorry.
Man!
You always lecture me, old man!
But I'm not that little prankster
that you think I am!
Humph!
Man, I'm going to get scolded later...
This kid who could only
express himself with pranks...
Okay, fine!
Huh...?!
If you insist...
I'll have you do a Rank C mission...
You'll be bodyguards for someone.
Really?!
Ah-ha!
Who? Who?
A feudal lord?!
Or, a princess?!
Don't get so hasty.
I'll introduce you now!
Could you please come in...?
Huh...?!
What's this? It's just a bunch
of damned squirts!
Huh...?
Particularly you, the smallest one
with the idiot face.
Are you really a Ninja?
Who's the smallest one with
the idiot face he's talking about...?
What?!
I'll kill him!!
What good will it do to
kill the old man
you're supposed to be
guarding, you moron?!
I'm Tazuna,
veteran bridge builder.
You'll be risking life and limb
in guarding me to the max
until I return to my land and
complete my bridge!
All right!
We're off!!
What're you so excited about?!
You see, I've never left
the village before!
Hey! Am I really okay with this squirt?!
I'm a Jonin. I'll be watching him.
There's no need to worry.
...okay with this squirt?!
Anyone but this old dude, man...
He's really the worst client!
I'll tell him a thing or two...
Hey, old man!
Don't be mocking Ninja
so much!
I'm awesome, you see!
I'm a super-elite Ninja who
will be called Hokage one day!
My name's Uzumaki Naruto.
Remember it well!!
The Hokage's the super top-dog
Ninja in the village, right?
You sure as hell don't seem like
you could become the Hokage...
Ahh! Shut up!
I'm prepared to do whatever
it takes to become the Hokage!
You'll have no choice
but to acknowledge me then!!
I'll never acknowledge you, squirt...
Even if you become the Hokage!
What?! I'll kill you!
I told you to stop it, you moron!
No! At least let me have
one shot, just one...
Say... Tazuna-san...?
What is it?
Your country is
"The Land of the Waves," right?
What of it?
Say, Kakashi-sensei...
Are there Ninja in that land, too?
No, there aren't Ninja in
the Land of the Waves...
But in other nations, while cultures
and customs are different,
hidden villages exist,
and there are Ninja there.
To the many nations on the continent,
the existence of Shinobi Villages is
a measure of the nation's military strength.
In other words,
that is how these nations maintain
their relationships with neighboring nations.
Even so, the villages are not
under the control of the nations.
They are equal in rank.
On a small island like
the Land of the Waves,
where it is difficult to be
influenced by other nations,
there is no need
for a Shinobi village.
Among the respective nations
that possess a Shinobi Village,
the five nations of "Fire," "Water,"
"Lightning," "Wind," and "Earth,"
due to their large territory and
immeasurable power,
are called the "Five Great Nations."
The Village Hidden in the Leaves
of the Land of Fire,
the Village Hidden in the Mist
of the Land of Water,
the Village Hidden in the Clouds
of the Land of Lightning,
the Village Hidden in the Sand
of the Land of Wind,
the Village Hidden in the Rocks
of the Land of Earth.
Only the leaders of
each of these Hidden Villages
are allowed to have
the name of Kage, the Shadow.
The "Hokage"
(Fire shadow),
"Mizukage"
(Water Shadow),
"Raikage"
(Lightning Shadow),
"Kazekage"
(Wind Shadow),
"Tsuchikage"
(Earth Shadow),
the so-called
Five Kage (shadows),
reign supreme over
the tens of thousands of Ninja
in each nation
of the whole world.
No kidding...
Hokage-sama is that incredible!
I wonder if that blah old man
is really that incredible...
Sounds fishy!
That can't be true! No way!
Hey!
You guys just doubted
Hokage-sama now, didn't you...?
Well... don't worry.
There are no Ninja battles
in Rank C missions.
Then, there's no worry of getting
into a scrape with foreign Ninja...!
Of course, not.
— What?!
— Huh?!
W-What?
The first one!
K-Kakashi-sensei!
The second one...
Oh...!
Hm?!
It doesn't come off!
W... Wow!!
Whoa!
Ugh!!
They'll come!
I have to do it...
I have to!!
Get back, sir!!
Yo...
Kakashi-sensei...! He's alive!
Humph!
Show off...
Wha...?!
Then, what was that...?
So Kakashi-sensei... used Substitutions...
Naruto...
Sorry I didn't help you right away...
I got you hurt.
I didn't think you'd be
incapable of moving...
I was saved, somehow...
Anyhow, let me just say,
good job, Sasuke.
You, too, Sakura.
I... couldn't do anything...
but Sasuke...
It was his first real battle...
Didn't he feel scared, at all?
He saved me like it was nothing and
without getting any dirt on his clothes...
Hey...
Huh?!
Are you hurt...
scaredy cat...?
— Sasuke!
— Naruto!
These guys have poison
on their claws.
You need to
take out the poison quickly.
What?!
You have to open the wound and
drain the poisoned blood.
Don't move so much.
The poison will spread.
By the way, Tazuna-san...
W-What is it...?!
I have something
to talk to you about.
Chunin from the
Village Hidden in the Mist...
These guys are Shinobi known for
continuing to fight
no matter what the sacrifice.
How were you able
to detect our movements?
There probably wouldn't be
puddles of water
on a clear day like today,
when it hasn't rained for days.
Knowing that, why'd you leave it
to the kids to fight?
If I felt like it,
I could kill these guys instantly...
But...
I had to know...
who the target
of these enemies was...
Hm?! What do you mean?
In other words...
what I mean is I had to know
if it was you,
or one of us Shinobi...
who was being targeted.
We haven't heard anything about
you being targeted by Shinobi.
The content of the request was
supposed to just be
protection from gangs,
thieves, and the like...
This is a mission with
a B rank or higher.
The request was supposed to be
for backup protection
until you finished building your bridge...
If our enemies were to be Ninja,
the mission would've been
estimated without question
as an expensive
"B Rank" mission.
It appears there's some kind
of good reason for this,
but being lied to in the request
won't do.
This is beyond the scope
of our mission.
This mission is too soon for us...
Let's give it up!
We need an anesthetic to
open Naruto's wound
and get out the poisoned blood...
We have to return to the village
and take him to a doctor...
Hmmm...
Hm? What...?!
This sure is a burden!
Since we need to treat Naruto's wound,
shall we go back to the village...?
— Huh!
— Oh!
Why am I so different?!
Why's it always me...
Damn it!
Naruto! What're you doing?!
I should be getting stronger...
Here I'm steadily carrying
out missions and
doing special-skill training
by myself every day...
I'll never get into another situation
from which I'll have to be rescued.
I'll never be afraid
or a be a coward...
I won't lose to Sasuke...
I'm going to swear on
the pain of my left hand!
I'll protect you, old man...
with this Kunai knife!!
The mission continues!!
Naruto...
It's all well and good to
rid yourself of the poisoned blood,
but any more than that and
you'll bleed to death.
Things will get hairy if you don't
stop the bleeding quick... Seriously!
Yikes!
Argh! No! No!
I can't die like this!
Show me your hand.
No! Help me!!
Naruto!
You're really self-abusive,
aren't you!
That's masochistic!
The wound is...
already starting to heal...
Um... um...
Am I okay?
You look awfully serious...
Well... You should be okay.
Is it... the power of
the Nine-Tailed Fox...?
Did you say you failed?!
I paid a lot of money to hire
you guys
because you said
you were once hot-shot Ninja!
Stop your damned grumbling...!!
Next time, I'll kill him with this...
head chopper!
I-It's really okay, right?!
It seems that the enemy
has hired good Shinobi...
On top of that, a tightened guard
on account of the Demon Brothers' failure
means that it won't be easy...
Just who do you think I am?!
This Momochi Zabuza,
who is called the demon of...
the Hidden Mist!!
Cultivate your hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain, never coming down.
Break into the contents, never falling down.
My knee is still shaking, like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting for people like me.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
'Cause you will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to look so wise.
Don't cry 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry...
We've finally landed ashore
in the Land of the Waves.
The guys before were
all well and good,
but there should be even
stronger guys lying in wait.
Okay! I'm going to regain
my honor and continue the mission.
No matter what enemy comes,
I'll protect the old man
this time around for sure.
Oh, they wasted no time.
An impressive-looking guy with
a huge Katana has come.
Next episode:
"The Assassin of the Mist!"
I'm going to kick butt once again!